Excuse me, sir. Sir, is this your
Bugatti? It is. And what did you do to
be able to afford a Bugatti? One second.
We We have one of the biggest media
channels in the entire world. We grew a
channel to 10 million followers. Could
we get one quick minute with you? One of
my friends. What's that? I think you
interviewed one of my friends. We
interviewed one of your friends? Yes.
I'm an entrepreneur. You're an
entrepreneur? I am. How many businesses
do you own? I've owned several over the
past few decades. Yeah. You think we
could interview you for one minute real
quick? Sure. So, what business has made
you the most money? The car business.
You're in the car business. I am in the
car business. What was the most amount
of money that you made in a single year?
Well, I did 80 million in one day. You
did 80 million in one day. Yeah.
Serious. Were you a good student in
school? I was a horrible student in
school. I had ADD. They didn't know what
it was back then. But it's actually been
a blessing. What's a lesson about
business you'd give to somebody that
they will not be taught in school. The
world will teach you if you listen. You
see the difference between Elon Musk
launching rockets all the time that blow
up and he learns from everyone or Boeing
waiting 5 years to put up one perfect
that then doesn't work. The difference
is don't be afraid to take a chance. If
you don't swing, you'll never hit a home
run. What is the best life advice you
could give to any 20-year-old watching
this right now? The biggest decision you
make in your life is the wife that you
marry. If they don't love what you do,
then you're going to have friction. You
got to find somebody who becomes part of
the solution, not the problem.
Absolutely not. What time are you coming
home? It's almost the opposite. My wife
loves what we do, and I have to drag her
out of the office sometimes cuz she
shares the same passion. How old are you
now? I am 65. Whose generation works
harder yours than mine? Uh, we'll see.
After this last election, I am a whole
lot more optimistic. I think your
generation is cut to go do great